(Amy:)So, listen, Sheldon, I was thinking...
...since this is our first Halloween
party as boyfriend and girlfriend...
(Amy:)...I thought it might be fun for us
to go in a couples' costume.
(Sheldon:)I couldn't agree more.
(Amy:)Really? I find that inconsistent
with everything I know about you.
Couples' costumes are one of
the few benefits of being in a relationship.
Now, imagine this:
(Sheldon:)You and I, entering Stuart's party...
(Sheldon:)...and all eyes turn to see America's
most beloved and glamorous couple:
- Yeah?
- R2-D2 and C-3P0.
Dibs on '3P0.
Sheldon, when I said couples' costume,
I meant, like, Romeo and Juliet...
(Amy:)...or Cinderella and Prince Charming.
(Amy:)Not two robots
from some silly movie I don't even like.
(Leonard:)Okay.
(Sheldon:)I'm gonna let that slide because
I know you're hopped up on tea bags.